ANDREW STORROW

Software developer with four years of experience working on large projects for organizations such as Norwegian Cruise Lines and the Texas Department of Public Safety. Varied career driven by a passion for learning with experience in fields such as GPS mapping, audio production, music and design. Located in San Diego, CA, available to start immediately.

EXPERIENCE

Bonefide Productions, Form Designer

February 2017 - Present, Remote (Part Time, Remote) Design and create PDF contract forms using a combination of Adobe Illustrator and Acrobat. Complete work while adhering to a high quality standard and level of detail. Utilize Javascript to increase interactivity in the PDFs.

Stone Impressions, Production Team Member

June 2019 - March 2020, San Diego, CA

Responsible for hand picking stone tiles that would best suit each customer's order. High attention to detail required with a focus on the visual appearance of the stone and the graphic pattern to be printed on it. Work done in a warehouse setting with frequent use of a fork lift and power tools. Laid off due to COVID-19.

Davey Resource Group, GIS Field Technician

July 2014 - May 2015, Austin, TX

Conducted GIS field inventory work for a large electric utility cooperative. Tagged and mapped subsections of their utility infrastructure adhering to strict quality standards and specifications, using Trimble GPS hardware and Clearion Mobile GIS mapping software. Worked outside in all weather elements.

Microassist, Inc, Web Application Developer

April 2012 - April 2013, Austin, TX

Implemented new features for the Texas Department of Public Safety Sex Offender Registry website. Completed using C# and ASP.NET, features included search functionality, individual rap-sheet viewing (using XSLT) and registry updates (using SQL Server).

StormFrog, Inc, Web Developer

June 2008 - July 2010, Victor, NY

Created and updated websites for a broad spectrum of clients. Tasks ranged from site layout and design using HTML/CSS, to creating reusable modules with ASP.NET and SQL Server. Worked heavily with a custom CMS based off of DotNetNuke.

CONTACT



585.298.0076



✓ andrew.storrow@gmail.com



San Diego CA, 92111



B.S. Software Eng., RIT

TECHNOLOGY



</>
Python C#/.NET

Java

 $\mathbb{C}++$

SQL

HTML5/CSS3

JavaScript

Git/GitHub

Bootstrap

Wordpress

ColdFusion

SOFTWARE



Adobe CC (Photoshop,

Illustrator.

InDesign, XD,

Premiere Pro)

Microsoft Office

Visual Studio

PyCharm

Google Drive

Dropbox

Pro Tools

Logic Pro X

Ableton Live

Andrew Storrow Page 2

PART-TIME & CONTRACT

Internal Revenue Service, Clerk (Seasonal)

February 2019 - May 2019, Austin, TX

Received tax returns, correspondence and documents in the mail and sorted into the appropriate categories. Removed content from envelopes, arranged in specific order and date stamped accordingly. Performed other duties as assigned.

Ascensus College Savings, Client Services Processor (Contract)

November 2016 - February 2017, Newton, MA

Processed a high volume of transactions, financial and account related, for College Savings 529 plans. Required a high attention to detail while also being as efficient as possible.

Campaign For Vermont, Technical Advisor

February 2016 – November 2016, Montpelier, VT Managed the online presence of a grass roots political organization. Updated the website and social media, sent out email newsletters and maintained the supporter database.

Sierra Trading Post, Retail Associate (Operations)

October 2015 – February 2016, Burlington, VT Organized and processed all incoming store goods, picked and packed web orders for customers, assumed responsibility as cashier when needed.

EDUCATION

American Graphics Institute

Certificate in User Experience Design

The Recording Consveratory of Austin

Professional Training in Audio Engineering

Rochester Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Science, Software Engineering